easysendy.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy and Copyright - EasySendy Pro

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, EasySendy collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. EasySendy’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how EasySendy’s visitors use its website. From time to time, EasySendy may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

EasySendy also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on EasySendy’s blogs. EasySendy only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

Any personal information which is collected by EasySendy will be used by us only in accordance with current data protection legislation

 **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to EasySendy’s websites choose to interact with EasySendy in ways that require EasySendy to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that EasySendy gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for Sendy hosting services at EasySendy.com to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with EasySendy – by purchasing access to the Amazon SES service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, EasySendy collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with EasySendy. EasySendy does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

 **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

EasySendy discloses potential personally-identifying information only to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on EasySendy’s behalf or to provide services available at EasySendy’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using EasySendy’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. EasySendy will not rent or sell potential personally-identifying information to anyone, other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations as described above. EasySendy discloses potential personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when EasySendy believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of EasySendy, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an EasySendy website and have supplied your email address, EasySendy may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with EasySendy and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. EasySendy takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. EasySendy uses cookies to help EasySendy identify and track visitors, their usage of EasySendy website, and their website access preferences. EasySendy visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using EasySendy’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of EasySendy’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

 **Comments**

Comments and other content submitted to our Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

 **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, EasySendy may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and is EasySendy’s sole discretion. EasySendy encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Should EasySendy decide to change its Privacy Policy, we will post such changes on this page so that you are always aware of how we use your personal information and in what circumstances we disclose it. Client’s continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute Client’s acceptance of such change.

 **For Customers in Europe and GDPR implications**

The users / customers of EasySendy, you need to take care of the following:

 **1\. Right to be forgotten**

As EasySendy Pro users / customer you have right to close your EasySendy Pro account anytime, anywhere from [EasySendy Pro accounts area](https://easysendy.com/docs/cancel-easysendy-pro-account/).

 **2\. Right to Rectify or Access**

As EasySendy Pro users / customers, you have every right to access your account information or modify it if required from accounts panel after [login](https://app.easysendy.com/).

 **3\. Right to Privacy Protection**

EasySendy Pro does everything in its hands to safeguard their customer’s data. In fact, we have created user groups to decide on who can access what resource from the application.

 **4\. Right to Data Portability**

As EasySendy Pro customers you have an option to move your data. You can export your data such as email lists, api keys, bounce/delivery servers, email box monitors, campaigns, campaign tags, lists, messages, sending domains, tracking domains, suppression lists, templates, template categories, subscriber profile per list, campaigns sent to a particular subscriber etc. from within your EasySendy Pro account. Check this [tutorial guide](https://easysendy.com/docs/how-to-export-your-easysendy-pro-accounts-data/).

 **5\. Right to be informed about a Breach**

Dataaegis Software Pvt. Ltd. (EasySendy Pro parent company) is required / committed to send a mass email notification to all EasySendy Pro users / customers if there is any form of data breach on site. You should immediately know when they are affected.

 **6\. Abide by Age Restrictions**

EasySendy Pro default age is set to 16 years. You can update this information from [here in your account](https://easysendy.com/docs/how-to-add-date-of-birth-in-your-account/).

 **DMCA Website Notice**

If you believe a EasySendy customer on a site hosted by EasySendy is infringing your copyright, please send a written notice to:

EasySendy,  
Dataaegis Software Pvt. Ltd.  
#1190/18, Anjanadri Avenue, 2nd Floor, 26th Main Rd,

JayaNagar 9th Block, Bengaluru, Karnataka-68, India.  

Section 512(c) of the DMCA requires that a notice include all of the following in order to be valid:

  * A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
  * Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or if multiple copyrighted works at a single site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site;
  * Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit EasySendy to locate the material;
  * Information reasonably sufficient to permit EasySendy to contact you, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an e-mail address;
  * A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
  * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are copyright owner or authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

You acknowledge that if you fail to comply with all of the foregoing requirements your DMCA notice may not be valid and EasySendy may take no action. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

 **EasySendy.com**  
<https://easysendy.com/>
